

Dominik Maslanka

Product Owner

d.m.maslanka@gmail.com



+48668602265



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ dominikmaslanka/



Experience

TransactionLink - Product Lead

Jan 2021 - Present (3 mon)

Responsible for managing the strategy and development of Fintech Marketplace. After 3 months we cover full Polish open banking coverage for AISP, Integrate multiple apps I.e. identity verification service, verification transfers and fraud detection. Successfully transform development process from scrum to Kanban + DevOps. Successfully introduces customer first model and Outcomes above outputs

Cobiro.com - Product Owner

Jan 2021 - Jul 2021 (7 mon)

Responsible for Cobiro payment system including integrations with Adyen, ChargeBee and E-commerce web app based on JamStack. After 3 months we build fully workable solution as MVP that allow Merchant to create a shop, sell products and Integrate it with PayPal wallet and other systems like Facebook Shops or via API2Cart - with WooCommerce, PrestaShop, Magento or Shopify

Dodax / myWorld.com - Product Owner

Dec 2018 - Dec 2020 (2 year)

Responsible for managing the strategy and development of a backstage e-commerce management system for 12 brand new e-commerce stores in Europe (MyWorld) and 12 Dodax stores, inc. Japan, USA, and Canada (CMS, Configuration & Content mgmt systems, Customer Service tools)

This is achieved with cross-functional scrum teams (a total of 9-12 team members) reporting directly to me. The team members were located in Switzerland, Austria, and Poland, making frequent travels a must to connect with team members and cultivate a team playing environment.

Part of my daily business responsibilities includes stakeholder management and collaboration with SME's in SEO and Digital Marketing teams. Progress of all projects is reported regularly to the CPO, CEO, VP Engineering.

Achievements:

- Development and roll-out of the CMS that supports the ecommerce platform and GPDR compliant anonymization system
- Building generic components architecture in compliance with information architecture modeling and best UX
- Implementation of Objective and Key results framework
- Reducing cost per ticket for Customer Service by over

Sport2Go.pl - Product Manager

Jan 2016 - Nov 2018 (2 years 11 months)

Responsible for managing the operation strategy and development of the marketplace and reservation app (mobile & web client - SaaS) for the Tennis Industry. Co-defining the product vision with business owners, and working closely with engineering team, sales, marketing, and support to ensure revenue and customer satisfaction.

Achievements:

- Onboarding more than 100 users active users on MVP release day date with more than 150 sold court and training hours
- Building fully async scrum team.

Sociologist, Tech-researcher, Project Coordinator

Dec 2015 - Jan 2018 (2 years 2 months)

As a tech-researcher, I was happy to work for such clients as Ericsson, Warsaw University, Coders Trust Poland (multi-onlineopen-course), Profile (Marketing Agency), VegeKiosk(FCMG). The main part of my business was focused on creating reports & expert opinions. Clients pertained to the analysis of trends, competition.

About me



Dedicated product owner/manager with 5 years of experience in the industry. Resourceful and works well under pressure. Very good interpersonal and communication skills. A motivational leader with a proven ability to help employees stay on task and happy. Successful in meeting deadlines.

My top Gallup's Clifton Strengths are: Input, Individualisation, Learner, Restorative & Responsibility.

Education



Bachelor in Computer Science WIT Warsaw school of Information Technology (2017-2020)

Msc in Sociology

University of Warsaw, Institute of Sociology (2012-2017)

Social Entrepreneurship

Certifications



DevOps

PeopleCert (ID: GR680000591DM)

Design Thinking SHOPA - Design & Strategy

ITIL Foundation v4 PeopleCert (ID: GR671188108DM)

Prince2 InProgress (ID: GR633111177DM)

Professional Skills



UX	Prototy	Prototyping		Agi	ile	OKR	
E-commerce		Usability		Scrum		JIRA	
DevOps	Mobi	Mobile		igital Strategy		KANBAN	
HotJar	Paym	Payments		Product Discovery			